Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Secretary's office, Yale University, records
1899-1953
RU 49
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
159.75
The records consist of correspondence, subject files, reports, and related materials concerning alumni relations, Corporation affairs, the dedication and use of Yale buildings, commemorations and memorials, commencement activities, Yale traditions, honorary degrees, lectures, prizes, and war activities. Also included are records of the Council Committee on Publications, and annual reports from schools, departments, and offices.
Yale University. Office of the Secretary
Farnam, Thomas Wells, 1877-1943
Hutchins, Robert Maynard, 1899-1977
Lohmann, Carl A. (Carl Albert), 1887-
Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1874-1958
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-A (YRG 4-A), Records of the Yale secretary"s office.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Related Material
Records of the secretary"s office, Yale University (RU 52), (Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library.)
Thomas Wells Farnam Papers (MS 659), (Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library.)
Anson P. Stokes Family Papers (MS 299), (Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library.)
George Frederick Gundelfinger Papers (MS 693), (Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library.)
Biographical / Historical
The Secretary is an administrative officer elected by the Corporation on nomination of the President. The Secretary prepares and keeps the records of the Corporation and in addition to being responsible for the safekeeping of the seal and other official University insignia, also supervises the election of Alunmi Fellows to the Corporation, helps the President prepare all diplomas and certificates of award, and is responsible for the management of all official University functions and publications. The Secretary works with a staff of associates which oversees such non-academic areas as the Yale Police Department, the University Archives, the University Council, public information, University security, and community relations.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, subject files, reports, and related materials concerning alumni relations; Corporation affairs; the dedication and use of Yale buildings; commemorations and memorials; commencement activities; Yale traditions; honorary degrees; lectures; prizes; war activities. Also included are records of the Council Committee on Publications and annual reports from schools, departments, and offices.
The records span the administrations of the following secretaries: Anson Phelps Stokes (1899-1921), Thomas W. Farnum, acting (1921-1923), Robert M. Hutchins (1923-1927), and Carl A. Lohmann (1927-1953).
Arrangement
The records are arranged as follows: I. Letterbooks of Anson Phelps Stokes, 1899-1921. II. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1899-1929. III. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1929-1953. IV. Subject Files, 1899-1953.
Commencement ceremonies; Degrees, Academic; Lectures and lecturing; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University -- Awards; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University -- Degrees; Yale University -- Public relations; Yale Corporation; Yale University. Office of the Secretary
- Letterbooks of Anson Phelps Stokes, 1899-1921; Series I
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - 3 vols, 1899-1900 [not chronological] (Box 1A)
  - 1900 October-1901 October (Box 2A, Folder 1-3)
  - 1901 October-1902 November (Box 3A, Folder 4-6)
  - 1902 November-1903 November (Box 4A, Folder 7-9)
  - 1903 November-1904 November (Box 5A, Folder 10-12)
  - 1904 December-1905 December (Box 6A, Folder 13-15)
  - 1905 December-1907 February (Box 7A, Folder 16-18)
  - 1907 February-November (Box 8A, Folder 19-20a)
  - 1907 July (Box 8A, Folder 20b)
  - 1907 November-1908 August (Box 9A, Folder 23)
  - 1908 August-1909 May (Box 10A, Folder 24-26)
  - 1909 May-1910 March (Box 11A, Folder 29)
  - 1910 March-November (Box 12A, Folder 30-32)
  - 1910 November-1911 April (Box 13A, Folder 33-34)
  - 1911 April-November (Box 14A, Folder 35-36)
  - 1911 November-1912 July (Box 15A, Folder 37-38)
  - 1912 July-1913 January (Box 16A, Folder 39-40)
  - 1913 January-May (Box 17A, Folder 41-42)
  - 1913 May-November (Box 18A, Folder 43-44)
  - 1913 November-1914 February (Box 19A, Folder 45-46)
  - 1914 February-June (Box 20A, Folder 47-48)
  - 1914 June-November (Box 21A, Folder 49-50)
  - 1914 November-1915 March (Box 22A, Folder 51-52)
  - 1915 March-July (Box 23A, Folder 53-54)
  - 1915 July-1916 April (Box 24A, Folder 55-56)
  - 1916 April-1917 March (Box 25A, Folder 57-58)
  - 1917 March-September (Box 26A, Folder 59-60)
  - 1917 September-1918 June (Box 27A, Folder 61-63)
  - 1918 June-1919 January (Box 28A, Folder 64-65)
  - 1919 January-May (Box 29A, Folder 66-67)
  - 1919 May-November (Box 30A, Folder 68-69)
  - 1919 November-1920 April (Box 31A, Folder 70-71)
  - 1920 April-November (Box 32A, Folder 72-73)
  - 1920 October-1921 May (Box 33A, Folder 74-75)
  - 1921 May-July (Box 34A, Folder 76)
  - Letter books of Executive Assistant to Secretary Stokes Edwin Rogers Embree, 1911 July-1921 September (Box 35A)
  - Letter books of Executive Assistant to Secretary Stokes Edwin Rogers Embree, 1912 September-1914 June (Box 35A)
- Anson Phelps Stokes correspondence and subject files, 1899-1929; Series II
  - A-Ah, 1900-1929 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - Abbott, Lyman, 1913-1919 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abbott, Mather A., 1917-1921 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Adams, George B., 1900-1921 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adams, John C., 1910-1919 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Aeronautical Society, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Aerial photographing, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ai-Al, 1900-1929 (Box 2, Folder 10-13)
  - Aiken, Alfred L., 1911-1925 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Albertson, Charles C., 1911-1913 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Aldis, Owen F., 1910-1912 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Allen, Frederic W., 1911-1921 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Allen, Phillip R., 1912-1913 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Allen, William S., 1910-1912 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Advisory Board, 1906-1910, 1918, 1920-1922, 1924, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 20-24)
  - Alumni Associations, visits to, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Council, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Alumni Fellows, 1923, 1925-1929 (Box 3, Folder 27-33)
  - Alumni University Day, 1926-1927 (Box 3, Folder 34-35)
  - Alumni University Day, 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 36-37)
  - Alumni War Memorial, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 38-39)
  - Am, 1915-1928 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - American Chemical Society, 1922-1923 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - American Child Hygiene Association, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - American Fellowships, Society for, in French Universities, 1919-1920 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - American Historical Association, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - American Relief Administration, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - American Universities on Exchange with France of Professors of Engineering and Applied Science, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - American University Union, 1917-1922 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - An, 1901-1929 (Box 4, Folder 48-49)
  - Anderson, William G., 1903-1928 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Andrews, Charles M., 1901-1928 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Angell, President James Rowland, 1907-1929 (Box 5, Folder 52-23)
  - Angier, Roswell P., 1910-1925 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Ap-Ar, 1903-1929 (Box 5, Folder 55-56)
  - Appointments, Bureau of, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 57-57a)
  - Archer, John C., 1915-1921 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Architectural Plan, Committee on, 1920-1921 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Armistice Day, 1922, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Armstrong, Walter P., 1912-1913 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Arndt, Dr. Paul, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - As-Ay, 1900-1917 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - As-Ay, 1918-1929 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Asakawa, Kan-Schi, 1903-1928 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Asher, Harry W., 1906-1919 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Associated Press statements, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Association of American Universities, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Atha, Albert H., 1911-1912 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Atterbury, Grosvenor, 1903-1919 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Atterbury, W.W., 1911-1913 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Atwood, Frank G., 1913-1930 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Avery, E.S., 1914 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Baa-Bak, 1900-1914 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Baa-Bak, 1915-1929 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Baccalaureate, 1912, 1921, 1923-1929 (Box 6, Folder 76-78)
  - Bacon, Benjamin W., 1903-1921 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Bacon, Harry, 1911-1920 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Bacon, William P., 1903-1915 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Bailey, William, 1909-1917 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Bailey, William B., 1907-1921 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Baitsall, George A., 1917-1922 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Bakewell, Charles M., 1905-1924 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Bal-Ban, 1901-1929 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Baldwin, Charles S., 1899-1911 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Baldwin, Simeon E., 1901-1920 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Bannard, Otto J., 1903-1927 (Box 7, Folder 89-91)
  - Bar, 1900-1929 (Box 8, Folder 92-96)
  - Barge, Benjamin F., 1900-1903 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Barnes, Jonathan, 1912-1913 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Barnum, Clara and Thomas R., 1907-1918 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Barnum, Walter, 1912-1915 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Barnum, William M., 1907-1921 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Barr, Charles J., 1917-1922 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Barrell, Joseph, 1903-1916 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Bas-Baz, 1902-1927 (Box 8, Folder 104-105)
  - Bass, Lyman M., 1913 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Bates, Lindell J., 1911-1913 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Baur, Paul V.C., 1907-1923 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Bea, 1902-1927 (Box 8, Folder 109-110)
  - Beach, Harlan P., 1903-1921 (Box 9, Folder 111-112)
  - Beach, John K., 1906-1919 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Beard, Augustus F., 1902-1925 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Beardsley, Guy E., 1911-1915 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Bec-Bed, 1914-1929 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Bec-Beh, 1902-1929 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Beebe, Frank H., 1907-1924 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Beebe, William, 1902-1918 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Beers, Henry A., 1903-1922 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Bei-Bel, 1903-1929 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Bell, J. Clement, 1913-1915 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Bement, Edward, 1908-1919 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Ben, 1902-1919 (Box 9, Folder 124-125)
  - Bennett, Mrs. Thomas G., 1909-1919 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Ber, 1905-1929 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Berdan, John M., 1903-1925 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Bergen, Frank, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Berger, George B., 1911-1913 (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - Bertram, S.R., 1905-1919 (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - Berzelius Society, 1913-1914, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 132)
  - Bes-Bey, 1907-1927 (Box 10, Folder 133)
  - Betts, Samuel R., 1902-1925 (Box 10, Folder 134-135)
  - Bi-Bil, 1900-1929 (Box 10, Folder 136-137)
  - Bicentennial, 1900-1901 (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - Bigelow, F.L., 1910-1913 (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Bim-Bis, 1900-1929 (Box 10, Folder 140-141)
  - Bingham, Hiram, 1906-1910 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Bingham, Hiram, 1911-1923 (Box 11, Folder 143-144)
  - Bingham Hall, 1926-1928 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - Bishop, Avard L., 1903-1923 (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - Bishop, Lottie G., 1915-1929 (Box 11, Folder 147-148)
  - Bissell, George P., 1913 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Bla-Ble, 1901-1929 (Box 11, Folder 150-151)
  - Black, Hugo, 1906-1920 (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - Black, Robert L., 1911-1913 (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Bland, Alan G., 1917 (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Bli, 1900-1929 (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - Blo-Bly, 1900-1929 (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Blount estate, 1907-1914 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - Blumer, George, 1906-1914 (Box 11, Folder 158-160)
  - Blumer, George, 1915-1920 (Box 12, Folder 161-164)
  - Boa-Bom, 1900-1929 (Box 12, Folder 165-166)
  - Bon-Boy, 1901-1929 (Box 12, Folder 167-170)
  - Bond, Henry R., 1913 (Box 13, Folder 171)
  - Bozell, Harold V., 1918-1920 (Box 13, Folder 172)
  - Bra, 1900-1929 (Box 13, Folder 173-174)
  - Bracker, Vasa K., 1907-1926 (Box 13, Folder 175)
  - Bre, 1900-1929 (Box 13, Folder 176)
  - Breckenridge, Lester P., 1909-1921 (Box 13, Folder 177)
  - Bri, 1900-1929 (Box 13, Folder 178)
  - Bright College Years, 1920-1921 (Box 13, Folder 179)
    General note
    See also: Series IV, boxes 274-275
  - Bristol, John W., 1900-1922 (Box 14, Folder 180-188)
  - Bro, 1901-1927 (Box 15, Folder 189-194)
  - Broadcasting, 1921-1928 (Box 15, Folder 195-196)
  - Brooks, Henry S., 1916-1917 (Box 15, Folder 197)
  - Brooks-Bryce Prize, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 198)
  - Brown, Charles R., 1907-1924 (Box 15, Folder 199-201)
  - Brown, Ernest W., 1911-1921 (Box 16, Folder 202)
  - Brown, William Adams, 1905-1928 (Box 16, Folder 203-204)
  - Bru-Bry, 1903-1929 (Box 16, Folder 205)
  - Bu-Bui, 1906-1929 (Box 16, Folder 206)
  - Bu-Bui, 1900-1929 (Box 16, Folder 207)
  - Budget, 1909-1920 (Box 16, Folder 208-209)
  - Buehler, Rev. H.G., 1912-1913 (Box 16, Folder 210)
  - Buildings [temporary], 1918 (Box 16, Folder 211)
  - Buildings, use of, 1923-1926 (Box 16, Folder 212)
  - Buildings, use of, 1924-1929 (Box 17, Folder 213-215)
  - Buildings, use of for concerts and lectures, 1926-1927 (Box 17, Folder 216)
  - Bul-Buz, 1900-1929 (Box 17, Folder 217-220)
  - Bumstead, Henry A., 1900-1920 (Box 17, Folder 221)
  - Bushnell, Rev. Samuel C., 1910-1912 (Box 17, Folder 222)
  - Buttrick, Wallace, 1907-1921 (Box 17, Folder 223)
  - Business courses, 1914-1915 (Box 18, Folder 224)
  - By, 1901-1921 (Box 18, Folder 225)
  - By-laws, 1915-1920 (Box 18, Folder 226)
  - Ca-Cai, 1900-1929 (Box 18, Folder 227)
  - Cal-Cap, 1907-1929 (Box 18, Folder 228-230)
  - Camp, Walter, 1900-1917 (Box 18, Folder 231-233)
  - Camp, Walter: memorial, 1925-1927 (Box 18, Folder 234)
  - Camp, Walter: memorial dedication, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 235)
  - Camp, Walter: memorial invitations and lists, [1928?] (Box 18, Folder 236)
  - Campbell, Charles S., 1907-1921 (Box 19, Folder 237)
  - Campruki, Jose, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 238)
  - Car, 1901-1929 (Box 19, Folder 239-242)
  - Carle, Robert W., 1905-1921 (Box 19, Folder 243)
  - Canby, Henry S., 1915-1926 (Box 19, Folder 244)
  - Carrere & Hastings, 1899-1919 (Box 19, Folder 245)
  - Cas, 1901-1929 (Box 19, Folder 246-247)
  - Cason, Charles, 1914-1917 (Box 19, Folder 248)
  - Catlin, Charles C., 1907-1920 (Box 19, Folder 249)
  - Ce, 1916-1924 (Box 19, Folder 250)
  - Cha-Cham, 1903-1928 (Box 19, Folder 251)
  - Chan-Chap, 1900-1929 (Box 20, Folder 252)
  - Chapel, 1919-1922 (Box 20, Folder 253)
  - Chapel, Committee on, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 254)
  - Chapin, E. Barton, 1915-1918 (Box 20, Folder 255)
  - Chaplains, 1918 (Box 20, Folder 256)
  - Char-Chay, 1903-1926 (Box 20, Folder 257)
  - Chase, Frederick, 1909-1913 (Box 20, Folder 258)
  - Che, 1906-1926 (Box 20, Folder 259)
  - Cheney, Howell, 1903-1927 (Box 20, Folder 260-262)
  - Cheney, Mary Bushnell, 1911-1912 (Box 20, Folder 263)
  - Chi, 1905-1923 (Box 20, Folder 264)
  - Chittenden, Alice Hill, 1912 (Box 20, Folder 265)
  - Chittenden, Russell H., 1899-1905 (Box 20, Folder 266-266)
  - Chittenden, Russell H., 1906-1918 (Box 21, Folder 268-278)
  - Chittenden, Russell H., 1919-1923 (Box 22, Folder 279-282)
  - Cho-Chy, 1902-1929 (Box 22, Folder 283)
  - Chronicles of American Motion Pictures, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 284)
  - Church, George H., 1914-1923 (Box 22, Folder 285)
  - Ci, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 286)
  - Civil War Memorial, 1913-1915 (Box 22, Folder 287)
  - Cla, 1901-1928 (Box 22, Folder 288-291)
  - Clark, Charles Hopkins, 1905-1925 (Box 23, Folder 292-294)
  - Clark, Charles Upson, 1903-1919 (Box 23, Folder 295-296)
  - Clark, John Emroy, 1901-1920 (Box 23, Folder 297)
  - Clarke, Charles Cameron, 1906-1929 (Box 23, Folder 298)
  - Class of 1853 fund, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 299)
  - Class records, 1926 (Box 23, Folder 300)
  - Claxton, P.P., 1913-1921 (Box 23, Folder 301)
  - Clay, Albert J., 1910-1924 (Box 23, Folder 302)
  - Cloister: list of men in the infirmary annex, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 303)
  - Cle-Cly, 1903-1929 (Box 23, Folder 304-305)
  - Clipping Service Curran & Mead, 1906-1908 (Box 23, Folder 306-307)
  - Clipping Service Curran & Mead, 1909-1911 (Box 24, Folder 308-310)
  - Clipping Service, 1915-1920 (Box 24, Folder 311-315)
  - Co-Col, 1902-1918 (Box 24, Folder 316-319)
  - Co-Col, 1919-1929 (Box 25, Folder 320-321)
  - Coffin Collection, 1902-1929 (Box 25, Folder 322)
  - Coffin, Henry Sloane, 1902-1929 (Box 25, Folder 323)
  - Cogswell, Ledyard Jr., 1911-1913 (Box 25, Folder 324)
  - Collections: Sunday openings, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 325)
  - Collections, Reports of the committee on, undated (Box 25, Folder 326)
  - Com-Cop, 1902-1929 (Box 25, Folder 327-331)
  - Commencement, 1904-1906 (Box 25, Folder 332)
  - Commencement, 1917-1919 (Box 25, Folder 333-335)
  - Commencement Platform, 1919 (Box 25, Folder 336)
  - Commencement, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 337)
  - Commencement: 1492 Dinner campus celebration, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 338)
  - Commencement, 1921-1923 (Box 26, Folder 339-343)
  - Commencement: directions for parade, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 344)
  - Commencement: railroad rates, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 345)
  - Commencement, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 346)
  - Commencement: Chief Marshall, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 347)
  - Commencement, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 348-349)
  - Commencement: Chief Marshall, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 350)
  - Commencement, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 351-352)
  - Commencement: Chief Marshall, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 353)
  - Commencement: suggested double plan, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 354)
  - Commencement, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 355-356)
  - Commencement: Chief Marshall, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 357)
  - Commencement: Platform, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 358)
  - Commencement, 1928 (Box 27, Folder 359-360)
  - Commencement, 1928 (Box 28, Folder 361)
  - Commencement: Chief Marshall, 1928 (Box 28, Folder 362)
  - Commencement: Platforms, 1928 (Box 28, Folder 363)
  - Commencement, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 364-365)
  - Commencement: Chief Marshall, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 366-367)
  - Commencement: Platforms, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 368)
  - Committee on the Common Freshman Year, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 369)
  - Committee on Coordination, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 370)
  - Committee on Organization and Program, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 371)
  - Committee on Relations with Foreign Universities, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 372)
  - Compton, George B., 1913-1915 (Box 29, Folder 373)
  - Conference Committee Minutes, undated (Box 29, Folder 374)
  - Connally, Thomas W., 1912-1915 (Box 29, Folder 375)
  - Convocation for the Crown Prince of Sweden, 1926 (Box 29, Folder 376)
  - Convocation for the Crown Prince of Sweden, 1926 (Box 29, Folder 377)
  - Convocation luncheon, 1926 (Box 29, Folder 378)
  - Cook, Albert S., 1902-1923 (Box 29, Folder 379)
  - Cooper, Clayton S., 1911-1913 (Box 29, Folder 380)
  - Cooper, James W., 1900-1915 (Box 29, Folder 381)
  - Cor-Cot, 1904-1926 (Box 29, Folder 382-383)
  - Corporation, 1908-1928 (Box 29, Folder 384)
  - Corporation luncheon, 1915 (Box 30, Folder 385)
  - Cortissoz, Royal, 1913 (Box 30, Folder 386)
  - Corwin, Robert N., 1903-1929 (Box 30, Folder 387-389)
  - Cory, Robert H., 1908-1922 (Box 30, Folder 390)
  - Cou-Coy, 1903-1929 (Box 30, Folder 391-392)
  - Cowan, Gilbert, 1908-1915 (Box 30, Folder 393)
  - Cra, 1903-1924 (Box 30, Folder 394)
  - Craig, Charles F., 1914-1920 (Box 30, Folder 395)
  - Cram, Ralph A., 1911-1920 (Box 30, Folder 396)
  - Crane, Z. Marshall, 1911-1913 (Box 30, Folder 397)
  - Crawford, Alfred Beecher, 1914-1921 (Box 30, Folder 398-399)
  - Crawford, Alfred Beecher, 1922-1929 (Box 31, Folder 400-401)
  - Crawford, Jack R., 1909-1919 (Box 31, Folder 402)
  - Cre, 1913-1925 (Box 31, Folder 403)
  - Crees, Henry W., 1909-1913 (Box 31, Folder 404)
  - Crenshaw, Lewis D., 1913-1917 (Box 31, Folder 405)
  - Cri-Cry, 1900-1923 (Box 31, Folder 406-408)
  - Cross, Wilbur L., 1902-1919 (Box 31, Folder 409-411)
  - Cross, Wilbur L., 1920-1929 (Box 32, Folder 412-412)
  - Cu, 1900-1929 (Box 32, Folder 414-416)
  - Curtis, Edward L., 1906-1911 (Box 32, Folder 417)
  - Curtiss, Julian W., 1903-1917 (Box 32, Folder 418)
  - Curtiss-Way Company, 1914-1915 (Box 32, Folder 419)
  - Cushing, Dr. Harvey, 1906-1934 (Box 32, Folder 420)
  - Cuyler, Thomas D., 1905-1919 (Box 32, Folder 421)
  - Da-Dan, 1904-1915 (Box 32, Folder 422)
  - Da-Dan, 1916-1928 (Box 33, Folder 423)
  - Daggett, David, 1904-1927 (Box 33, Folder 424)
  - Daggett, Leonard M., 1909-1919 (Box 33, Folder 425)
  - Dana, Edward S., 1899-1927 (Box 33, Folder 426-427)
  - Dana, J. Dwight, 1911-1925 (Box 33, Folder 428)
  - Dana, Richard H., 1911-1915 (Box 33, Folder 429)
  - Dances, 1924 (Box 33, Folder 430)
  - Danford, Robert M., 1916-1919 (Box 33, Folder 431)
  - Daniel, Winthrop M. Esq., 1923-1924 (Box 33, Folder 432)
  - Danielson, R.E., 1913 (Box 33, Folder 433)
  - Dar-Dat, 1905-1924 (Box 33, Folder 434)
  - Dav-Daw, 1907-1929 (Box 33, Folder 435-436)
  - Davenport, William B., 1907-1921 (Box 33, Folder 437)
  - Davis, Carl W., 1910-1915 (Box 33, Folder 438)
  - Davis, Walter G., Jr., 1912-1914 (Box 33, Folder 439)
  - Davison Scholarships, 1923-1926 (Box 34, Folder 440-441)
  - Day, 1902-1927 (Box 34, Folder 442-443)
  - Day, Clive, 1907-1926 (Box 34, Folder 444)
  - Day, Dwight H., 1907-1923 (Box 34, Folder 445)
  - Day, Frank Miles, 1917-1918 (Box 34, Folder 446)
  - Day, George P., 1908 March-1911 March (Box 34, Folder 447-451)
  - Day, George P., 1911 April-1914 August (Box 35, Folder 452-461)
  - Day, George P., 1914 September-1917 March (Box 36, Folder 462-469)
  - Day, George P., 1916 July-October (Box 36, Folder 470)
  - Day, George P., 1917 July-1920 June (Box 37, Folder 471-479)
  - Day, George P., 1920 July-1929 (Box 38, Folder 480-483)
  - De-Dey, 1902-1929 (Box 38, Folder 484-487)
  - DeCamp, Walter A., 1911-1921 (Box 38, Folder 488)
  - DeForest, Robert W., 1902-1929 (Box 39, Folder 489)
  - Degrees, 1906-1926 (Box 39, Folder 490)
  - Delamarre, Louis, 1913-1917 (Box 39, Folder 491)
  - Denison, Robert C., 1910-1919 (Box 39, Folder 492)
  - Departmental Charges, 1923-1924 (Box 39, Folder 493)
  - DeSilver, Albert Memorial Fund, 1926-1928 (Box 39, Folder 494)
  - Dettra, John M., 1910-1914 (Box 39, Folder 495)
  - Developmental Program for the University, 1910-1919 (Box 39, Folder 496-497)
  - Dexter, Franklin B., 1900-1920 (Box 39, Folder 498)
  - Di, 1902-1929 (Box 39, Folder 499-501)
  - Dickinson and Wheelock Halls, 1928-1929 (Box 39, Folder 502)
  - Diller, John C., 1928-1929 (Box 40, Folder 503)
  - Dimmick, J. Benjamin, 1909-1919 (Box 40, Folder 504)
  - Dinner, 1492 Class, 1915 (Box 40, Folder 505)
  - Divinity School, Yale University, 1922-1925 (Box 40, Folder 506)
  - Divisions, Suggested list of; submitted by Dean Cross, 1919-1920 (Box 40, Folder 507)
  - Do, 1900-1929 (Box 40, Folder 508-511)
  - Dodge Lectures, 1922-1923 (Box 40, Folder 512)
  - Dormitory, Campus Controversy, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 513)
  - Dr, 1903-1928 (Box 40, Folder 514)
  - Yale Dramatic Association, 1923 (Box 41, Folder 515)
  - Drury, Samuel S., 1910-1928 (Box 41, Folder 516)
  - Du-Dy, 1899-1929 (Box 41, Folder 517-520)
  - Duyckinck, Whitehead C., 1905-1918 (Box 41, Folder 521)
  - Dwight, Frederick, 1905-1918 (Box 41, Folder 522)
  - Dyer Memorial Fund, 1921-1922 (Box 41, Folder 523)
  - Ea-Ec, 1904-1925 (Box 41, Folder 524)
  - Eastman, W.W., 1914 (Box 41, Folder 525)
  - Eaton, George F., 1904-1927 (Box 41, Folder 526)
  - Ed, 1903-1929 (Box 41, Folder 527-528)
  - Eddy, Brewer, 1909-1920 (Box 42, Folder 529)
  - Eddy, Earnest A., 1911-1912 (Box 42, Folder 530)
  - Eddy, G. Sherwood, 1911-1919 (Box 42, Folder 531)
  - Eden, John H. Jr., 1913 (Box 42, Folder 532)
  - Edgerton, John W., 1904-1918 (Box 42, Folder 533)
  - Education, 1899-1920 (Box 42, Folder 534)